Jiang Zhaoguo.
장자오궈.
Don't hit it again!
다시는 때리지 마세요!
Quickly grab a knife
빨리 칼을 집어들고
knife!
칼!
Take the knife.
칼을 가져가세요.
Quickly grab a knife.
빨리 칼을 집으세요.
Why are you silent?
왜 침묵?
Knife!
칼!
The knife comes.
칼이 온다.
Kill him
그를 죽여
fast!
빠른!
Attack.
공격.
Kill him!
그를 죽여!
Quickly kill him!
빨리 그를 죽여라!
Fast!
빠른!
Why are you still silent?
왜 아직도 침묵하고 있습니까?
Quickly kill him!
빨리 그를 죽여라!
Fast!
빠른!
Quick, help me take care of this corpse.
빨리 이 시체를 처리할 수 있게 도와주세요.
Why are you still silent?
왜 아직도 침묵하고 있습니까?
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
Come in
올
why did you come home so late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 집에 왔어?
Didn't you hear?
못 들었어?
Recently our business has experienced big problems.
최근 우리 회사는 큰 문제를 겪었습니다.
Commander Luo arrested CCP members,
뤄 사령관은 중국 공산당원들을 체포했고,
and also the head of the transportation station.
그리고 교통국장이기도 합니다.
The level is not low
수위가 낮진 않네요
but I didn't think so
하지만 난 그렇게 생각하지 않았어
the CCP's underground party
중국 공산당 지하당
is the owner of the book and painting shop Yumo, owner Lu
책과 그림가게 유모의 오너 루씨입니다.
Lu's boss is the Underground Party of the Chinese Communist Party
루의 상사는 중국 공산당 지하당이다.
really didn't expect it
정말 예상하지 못했다
CCP underground party
중국 공산당 지하당
CCP special agents are everywhere.
중국 공산당 특수 요원은 어디에나 있습니다.
Because he is a leader,
그 사람이 리더이기 때문에,
there must be a lot of information.
정보가 많아야 합니다.
In that case,
그 경우,
will make a major contribution?
크게 기여할 것인가?
What report?
무슨 보고서요?
What services do you provide?
어떤 서비스를 제공하나요?
Boss Lu is in order to protect his colleagues,
루보스는 동료들을 보호하기 위해,
didn't say a word.
아무 말도하지 않았습니다.
Better to die than give up.
포기하는 것보다 죽는 것이 낫습니다.
I have heard
나는 들었다
CCP people are all brave
중국 공산당 사람들은 모두 용감합니다
you've seen it, right?
너 본 적 있지, 그렇지?
These are all Boss Lu's data,
모두 루보스의 데이터입니다.
and interrogation recordings.
그리고 심문 녹음.
I have to tidy everything up.
모든 것을 정리해야 해요.
Tomorrow we still have to hand it over to Commander Luo.
내일 우리는 그것을 Luo 사령관에게 넘겨야합니다.
How to make?
제조법?
I'll sleep for a while.
잠시만 자겠습니다.
Talk about it later.
나중에 그것에 대해 이야기하십시오.
You sleep quickly
너 빨리 자
why did you change your phone number
전화번호 왜 바꿨어?
I can't find you.
나는 당신을 찾을 수 없습니다.
I don't want to see you again
다시는 보고 싶지 않아
Why?
왜?
You asked me why
왜냐고 물으셨죠
don't you know what you have done
당신이 무슨 짓을 했는지 모르시나요?
How long will you lie to me?
언제까지 나한테 거짓말할 거야?
You...
너...
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
I don't have any feelings for that woman.
그 여자한테는 아무런 감정도 없어요.
She is Director Liu's daughter.
그녀는 류 감독의 딸이다.
I just need him...
난 그 사람이 필요할 뿐이야...
Helped me get some things done.
내가 몇 가지 일을 처리하는 데 도움이 되었습니다.
It turns out you can speak so confidently.
당신은 너무나 자신있게 말할 수 있다는 것이 밝혀졌습니다.
Now I'm in this position.
이제 나는 이 위치에 있다.
I have to take advantage
이점을 활용해야 해요
all the power around me that can be used.
내 주변에서 사용할 수 있는 모든 힘.
I can not do anything.
나는 아무것도 할 수 없습니다.
You don't understand politics,
정치를 이해하지 못하는군요.
you're too innocent
당신은 너무 결백해요
However,...
하지만,...
This is also the reason I love you.
이것이 내가 당신을 사랑하는 이유이기도 합니다.
Love me?
나를 사랑해?
You still say things like this now.
지금도 그런 말을 하시네요.
Isn't that very ironic?
참 아이러니하지 않나요?
Can we not discuss this matter first?
이 문제를 먼저 논의하면 안 될까요?
Ding Qiuyang was a member of the mountain's subordinate army.
Ding Qiuyang은 산의 예하 군대의 일원이었습니다.
This time I came to Shanghai for a secret mission.
이번에 나는 비밀 임무를 위해 상하이에 왔습니다.
If he knew,...
만약 그 사람이 알았다면...
The fighters will know I'm coming to Shanghai.
파이터들은 내가 상하이에 온다는 것을 알게 될 것이다.
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Looks like it's pretty close here.
여기가 꽤 가까운 것 같네요.
Wait
기다리다
how did you know Ding Qiuyang
딩추양을 어떻게 알았어?
help the mountain's subordinates.
산의 부하들을 도와주세요.
Back when you introduced me to him
당신이 나에게 그 사람을 소개했을 때
just said he was a famous director.
방금 그 사람이 유명한 감독이라고 하더군요.
Let's treat the corpse first.
먼저 시체를 처리합시다.
Perhaps not?
아마 아닐거야?
No.
아니요.
I told you to tell me now
지금 말하라고 했잖아
Good.
좋은.
Then I'll tell you
그럼 내가 말해줄게
that day at the Hollywood bar,
그날 할리우드 바에서
I've met him.
나는 그를 만난 적이 있습니다.
Why did you meet him?
그 사람을 왜 만났어요?
I was forced.
나는 강요당했습니다.
At that time, I had an important document in my hand.
그 때 내 손에는 중요한 문서가 들려 있었습니다.
He said if I take you away,
내가 당신을 데려가면, 그가 말했어요.
then will send me to the military headquarters.
그러면 나를 군 사령부로 보내겠습니다.
So,
그래서,
actually you were the one who sold me.
사실은 당신이 나를 팔았거든요.
That's right, right?
그렇죠?
What are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
How can I sell you?
어떻게 하면 당신을 팔 수 있나요?
I think first
내 생각엔 먼저
you really have to
넌 정말 그래야 해
that's why you can't take me away.
그렇기 때문에 당신은 나를 데려갈 수 없습니다.
I didn't think you were the ones who had negotiated it
나는 당신이 그것을 협상한 사람이라고 생각하지 않았습니다
what tactics
어떤 전술
What are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
I know.
알아요.
I know you can't possibly give up your career
당신이 경력을 포기할 수 없다는 걸 알아요
shan Xia said he can help you in your career
Shan Xia가 당신의 경력에 ​​도움을 줄 수 있다고 했어요
so I thought
그래서 나는 생각했다
wouldn't it be great if you
당신이라면 좋지 않을까요?
isn't that a good thing?
그거 좋은 일 아니야?
You're shameless!
당신은 뻔뻔해요!
Han Lu.
한루.
Cold dew.
차가운 이슬.
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원합니까?
let me go
나를 보내줘
Why
왜
Why?
왜?
Why did you have to hurt me like this?
왜 나에게 이렇게 상처를 주어야만 했나요?
You calm down a bit, okay?
좀 진정하세요, 알았죠?
Let's finish the body first.
먼저 본체를 완성해 보겠습니다.
I just told you.
내가 방금 말해줬 잖아.
Perhaps not?
아마 아닐거야?
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
If the Japanese know I'm coming to Shanghai,
일본인이 내가 상하이에 온다는 것을 안다면,
then I will die.
그러면 나는 죽을 것이다.
Understand?
이해하다?
You make me very sad
당신은 나를 매우 슬프게 만듭니다
lu Yousheng.
루 유성.
Correct
옳은
all the way is clear
모든 것이 분명하다
1927 AD
서기 1927년
join the Chinese Communist Party
중국 공산당에 가입하다
why should you join the Communist Party?
왜 공산당에 가입해야 합니까?
For faith's sake.
믿음을 위해서.
Do you understand what faith is?
믿음이 무엇인지 아시나요?
Of course I don't understand.
물론 이해가 안 돼요.
their names,
그들의 이름,
do you think I can say it?
내가 말할 수 있을 것 같아?
Of course I have a family.
물론 나에겐 가족이 있다.
Who doesn't have a family?
가족이 없는 사람이 어디 있나요?
It's just that I couldn't protect them well.
단지 내가 그들을 잘 지켜주지 못했을 뿐입니다.
Well.
잘.
I have many tasks.
나는 할 일이 많다.
Due to beliefs and doctrines
신념과 교리로 인해
you do not understand.
당신은 이해하지 않는다.
Then I'll say something you'll understand.
그러면 당신이 이해할 수 있는 말을 할게요.
My mission is
내 임무는
is to make every Chinese person
모든 중국인을 만드는 것입니다
when they got home
그들이 집에 왔을 때
what they see is not fear,
그들이 보는 것은 두려움이 아니라
not fear,
두려움이 아니라,
nor the cold corpses of his wife and child.
그의 아내와 아이의 차가운 시체도 아닙니다.
All he saw were the smiling faces of his family.
그가 본 것은 가족들의 웃는 얼굴뿐이었다.
Happiness.
행복.
But hope.
하지만 희망합니다.
This...
이것...
It's my job.
그건 내 일이야.
It is our duty to every communist
그것은 모든 공산주의자들에 대한 우리의 의무이다
do you understand?
이해했나요?
Have you written it down?
적어 놓으셨나요?
Good
좋은
I can't wait until that day comes
그날이 올 때까지 기다릴 수 없어
but there are people who will come.
하지만 올 사람들이 있어요.
40 thousand Chinese compatriots will wait until
4만명의 중국 동포들이 기다릴 것이다.
that day
그 날
referred to as the new China
신중국이라 불림
did someone steal the body?
누군가 시체를 훔쳤나요?
Ding Qiuyang is not dead at all?
Ding Qiuyang은 전혀 죽지 않았나요?
I was too careless.
나는 너무 부주의했다.
Why kill Ding Qiuyang?
왜 Ding Qiuyang을 죽입니까?
This time I came to Shanghai
이번에 상해에 왔어요
do you want to negotiate?
협상하고 싶니?
with a code name?
코드네임으로?
He holds something I want.
그 사람은 내가 원하는 것을 갖고 있어요.
But this thing
하지만 이건
the Japanese also wanted to get it.
일본인도 그것을 얻고 싶어했습니다.
Japanese people in Chongqing,
충칭에 사는 일본인,
put a lot of spies,
스파이를 많이 배치하고
so they already know
그래서 그들은 이미 알고 있어
chongqing sent people to Shanghai
충칭은 상하이에 사람을 보냈다
but they don't know
하지만 그들은 몰라
the one they sent was me
그들이 보낸 사람은 나였어
jika Ding Qiuyang ini
지카 딩 치우양 이니
told my identity to the Japanese
내 신분을 일본인에게 말했어
even said
심지어 말했다
the Japanese discovered the magpie before me,
일본인이 나보다 먼저 까치를 발견했고,
then my mission this time really failed.
그러다 이번 임무는 정말 실패했어요.
Then I can go find a mountain subordinate to test it.
그러면 산 부하를 찾아 시험해 보면 되겠군요.
Looking for what?
무엇을 찾고 계십니까?
Did Ding Qiuyang find the foot of the mountain?
Ding Qiuyang이 산기슭을 찾았나요?
Does the foot of the mountain know all this?
산기슭은 이 모든 것을 알고 있는가?
You can't go
넌 갈 수 없어
This is too dangerous.
이것은 너무 위험합니다.
Won't.
습관.
Why?
왜?
Because he loves me.
그 사람은 나를 사랑하기 때문이다.
What are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
He loves me.
그는 나를 좋아한다.
maybe,
아마도,
love me more than you
너보다 나를 더 사랑해
qian Xiu Cai
치안 슈 카이
koran
코란
here.
여기.
New declaration.
새로운 선언.
News report.
뉴스 보도.
Good.
좋은.
Not true.
사실이 아니다.
Why less than one page?
왜 한 페이지도 안 되나요?
Why is there one page less?
왜 한 페이지가 줄어들까요?
What's missing is the series page.
누락된 것은 시리즈 페이지입니다.
Fast.
빠른.
Help me search.
검색을 도와주세요.
Then I'll look for it.
그럼 제가 찾아보겠습니다.
This story is in a time of crisis,
이 이야기는 위기의 시대에,
zhen Fei ingin membunuh Jiang Xiao He.
Zhen Fei Ingin membunuh Jiang Xiao He.
Jiang Xiao He didn't know that he intended to kill.
장샤오는 자신이 죽이려는 의도를 갖고 있다는 사실을 몰랐습니다.
No.
아니요.
If not,
그렇지 않다면,
where are Captain Zhao and Manager Luo's newspapers?
자오 선장과 루오 감독의 신문은 어디에 있나요?
I've delivered it to the front door.
문앞까지 배달해줬어요
You can borrow them for a while.
잠시 동안 빌릴 수 있습니다.
Makes sense.
말이된다.
Finally back
마침내 돌아왔다
leader
지도자
the office has been cleaned.
사무실이 청소되었습니다.
As the saying goes, back to a new atmosphere
새로운 분위기로 돌아왔다는 말처럼
open the door to meet the far away
문을 열어 먼 곳을 만나다
Chen's head
첸의 머리
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Ketua Zhao.
케투아 자오.
Already home
이미 집에
surprise no?
놀랍게도 아니?
Safe, safe.
안전해요. 안전해요.
I'm looking for newspapers here.
나는 여기서 신문을 찾고 있어요.
What newspapers are you looking for at my place?
우리 집에서 어떤 신문을 찾고 있나요?
The martial arts novel featured in this new statement,
이 새로운 성명서에 등장하는 무협 소설은,
kun Lun who was surprised.
놀란 쿤룬.
I don't know why I didn't order anything
내가 왜 아무것도 주문하지 않았는지 모르겠어요
Qian Xiu said that the newspapers had been placed here
Qian Xiu는 신문이 여기에 놓여 있었다고 말했습니다
so I came to look for him
그래서 그를 찾으러 왔어요
have found?
찾았어?
Have found.
찾았습니다.
Here.
여기.
Look at it.
보세요.
Kun Lun?
쿤룬?
Captain Zhao is back.
자오 선장이 돌아왔습니다.
Your newspaper, I remain motionless.
당신의 신문, 나는 움직이지 않습니다.
I put it here.
여기에 넣었습니다.
You tell me after reading it.
읽어보신 후 말씀해 주세요.
I came to get it.
나는 그것을 얻으러 왔습니다.
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
Go ahead.
계속하세요.
Safe, safe.
안전해요. 안전해요.
What do you want, boss?
무엇을 원하시나요, 보스?
Undress.
알몸 상태.
Komandan Luo.
코만단 루오.
Can you still sit?
아직도 앉을 수 있나요?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Zhao An.
자오안.
You did not know?
너는 몰랐다?
Of course I know
당연히 알지
he was clearly an important person in the CCP that we arrested.
그는 분명히 우리가 체포한 중국 공산당의 중요한 인물이었습니다.
We didn't get any prizes.
우리는 어떤 상품도 받지 못했습니다.
Zhao An is back to work?
자오안(Zhao An)이 다시 일하러 왔나요?
On what basis?
무슨 근거로?
As expected.
예상대로.
Do you think Kimura will let him keep a horse?
키무라가 말을 키우도록 허락할 것 같나요?
What you mean is...
무슨 말이에요?
Already thought of a way to deal with Zhao An, right?
자오안을 상대할 방법은 이미 생각하고 있었죠?
We will monitor the changes.
변경 사항을 모니터링하겠습니다.
Don't want chaos.
혼란을 원하지 마십시오.
Old Fox.
올드폭스.
What are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 계신가요?
I've found it, I've found it.
찾았어요, 찾았어요.
There's another series to check out.
확인해 볼 만한 또 다른 시리즈가 있습니다.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
This Zhen Fei, still can't intervene.
이 Zhen Fei는 여전히 개입할 수 없습니다.
The tension will soon be revealed.
그 긴장감은 곧 드러날 것이다.
I still feel like the feeling here is not right.
아직도 이곳의 느낌이 맞지 않는 것 같아요.
Yesterday, when I opened the window all day, the wind was strong.
어제는 하루종일 창문을 열었는데 바람이 강했어요.
The smell is not right.
냄새가 안나요.
Basically not true.
기본적으로 사실이 아닙니다.
Salah.
살라.
This scent is simply not right
이 향은 정말 안 맞는 것 같아
there is no longer the smell of horse manure
더 이상 말똥 냄새가 나지 않아요
not accustomed to.
익숙하지 않습니다.
Sis,
언니,
if we go
우리가 가면
What about Xiao Douzi in the future?
앞으로 Xiao Douzi는 어떻게 될까요?
Don't think about Xiao Douzi anymore.
더 이상 Xiao Douzi에 대해 생각하지 마세요.
Village Chief Mu wants to expel him,
무 마을 이장은 그를 추방하고 싶어하는데,
from now on he is a Japanese horse.
이제부터 그는 일본 말입니다.
It will be better than our fate.
그것은 우리의 운명보다 나을 것입니다.
How did it happen?
어떻게이 일이 일어 났어요?
Who in Japan knows Xiao Douzi's habits?
일본에서 Xiao Douzi의 습관을 아는 사람은 누구입니까?
This seed likes to eat alfalfa.
이 씨앗은 알팔파를 좋아합니다.
He doesn't like peanuts.
그는 땅콩을 좋아하지 않습니다.
He likes rubber horse brushes.
그는 고무 말 브러시를 좋아합니다.
Doesn't like iron combs.
철제 빗을 좋아하지 않습니다.
Go with them.
그들과 함께 가십시오.
Don't be picky here
여기서 까다롭게 굴지 마세요
Just keeping a horse is no longer exciting.
말을 키우는 것만으로는 더 이상 흥미롭지 않습니다.
What do you think I can do with you?
내가 너한테 뭘 할 수 있을 것 같아?
Tree trunk.
나무 줄기.
Yesterday A-Chuan and Xiao Lai Zi.
어제 A-Chuan과 Xiao Lai Zi.
Pretty good.
꽤 좋아요.
Officially recruit them
공식적으로 모집하세요
I want to reorganize my troops
병력을 재편성하고 싶다
Good.
좋은.
10 shots.
10발.
Since childhood,
어린 시절부터,
never been humiliated like this.
이런 굴욕을 받은 적이 없습니다.
Or I hit myself.
아니면 나 자신을 때렸어요.
= Juara dunia = Luo Guanqun.
= Juara dunia = Luo Guanqun.
You have to remember.
당신은 기억해야합니다.
Want to embarrass Luo Guan Qun,
Luo Guan Qun을 당황하게 만들고 싶습니다.
should start from Chen Jia Ping
Chen Jia Ping부터 시작해야합니다
the one who went to the tea shop and took the old road was him
찻집에 가서 옛길을 택한 사람이 그 사람이더라
He was the one who came to the bookstore and made a mess.
서점에 와서 난장판을 만든 사람이 바로 그 사람이었다.
And also the action of arresting the negotiator yesterday.
그리고 어제 협상가를 체포하는 행동도요.
Every time something bad happens,
안 좋은 일이 일어날 때마다,
there must be him
그 사람이 틀림없어
Oh yes
바로 이거 야
Lao Tian's people wanted notice at that time,
당시 Lao Tian의 사람들은 통지를 원했습니다.
which newspaper is it in?
어느 신문에 실렸나요?
New statement?
새로운 성명?
Correct.
옳은.
This new statement includes a series of martial arts novels.
이 새로운 성명에는 일련의 무술 소설이 포함되어 있습니다.
Kun Lun was surprised.
쿤룬은 놀랐다.
I don't know why I didn't order anything
내가 왜 아무것도 주문하지 않았는지 모르겠어요
Qian Xiu said that the newspapers had been placed here
Qian Xiu는 신문이 여기에 놓여 있었다고 말했습니다
so I came looking for him.
그래서 그를 찾으러 왔어요.
Well then, missing person search notice,
그럼 실종자 수색 안내는,
It was a secret code for communication with the CCP
중국 공산당과의 통신을 위한 비밀 코드였습니다.
so why Chen Jiaping
그럼 왜 Chen Jiaping인가?
Want to make this new declaration soon?
이 새로운 선언을 곧 하고 싶습니까?
A-chuan as a fellow Xiao Lai Zi.
A-chuan은 Xiao Lai Zi의 동료입니다.
As they squatted in Yu Mo's calligraphy and painting shop,
유모의 서예화 가게에 쪼그려 앉아 있던 그들은
Chen Jia Ping also came
천지아핑도 왔어요
at that time he moved several villas and treasures.
그 당시 그는 여러 빌라와 보물을 옮겼습니다.
Do you think he meant something else?
그 사람이 다른 뜻으로 말한 것 같나요?
Panggil Qian Xiu Cai kesini
Panggil Qian Xiu Cai 케시니
Good
좋은
kapten Zhao,
캡텐 자오,
if you say it is also very strange
당신이 말한다면 그것도 아주 이상해요
Chen's section chief
첸 과장
I used to hate seeing new announcements.
나는 새로운 공지를 보는 것을 싫어했습니다.
It's all just a cliché,
다 클리셰일뿐??,
but don't know why lately
그런데 최근에는 왜 그런지 모르겠어요
very attentive to new reports.
새로운 보고에 매우 주의를 기울입니다.
Every day he immediately asked if the news had arrived or not
매일 그는 즉시 뉴스가 도착했는지 여부를 물었습니다.
I know.
알아요.
Get out.
나가세요.
Wait.
기다리다.
This is what I'm asking you
이것이 내가 당신에게 묻는 것입니다.
the thing I asked you.
내가 당신에게 물어본 것.
Understand?
이해하다?
Understand.
이해하다.
Ketua Zhao,
케투아 자오,
according to you, my observational abilities
당신 말에 따르면 내 관찰 능력은
not bad right?
나쁘지 않지?
Too good.
너무 좋은.
Ketua Zhao
케투아 자오
even though I'm just a doorman,
나는 단지 도어맨일 뿐이지만,
but I can still do it
하지만 난 아직 할 수 있어
other things and so on
다른 것 등등
what else do you want to do?
또 뭘 하고 싶어?
You just be the manager.
당신이 매니저가 되어보세요.
It's been a joke.
농담이었어.
Kapten Zhao.
캡텐 자오.
If there's anything, just call me.
무슨 일 있으면 나한테 전화해.
I go first
내가 먼저 가
Chen Jia Ping, these two days
Chen Jia Ping, 이 이틀 동안
why rush to see the new declaration
왜 새로운 선언을 서둘러 볼까?
because Lu is his boss.
루가 그의 상사이기 때문이다.
After Lao Lu died,
라오루가 죽은 후,
there will be a new boss who wants to work with him.
그와 함께 일하고 싶어하는 새로운 상사가 생길 것입니다.
And the secret code for this connection
그리고 이 연결의 비밀 코드는
it's in the new announcement.
새로운 공지에 있어요.
But all this,
하지만 이 모든 것은,
obituary announcements and others,
사망 기사 발표 및 기타
more clearly which is the secret connecting code,
더 명확하게는 비밀 연결 코드입니다.
we don't understand either.
우리도 이해가 안 돼요.
We don't understand.
우리는 이해하지 못합니다.
Someone understands
누군가는 이해한다
is indeed a genuine Bordeaux grape
진짜 보르도 포도다
Haven't tasted this taste in a long time.
이 맛을 오랫동안 맛보지 못했습니다.
Ketua Zhao.
케투아 자오.
Eat it.
그것을 먹을.
So I don't drink anymore.
그래서 더 이상 술을 마시지 않습니다.
If Brother Huang likes it,
황 형제님이 좋아하신다면,
I'll get someone to deliver a few more bottles.
몇 병 더 배달해 줄 사람을 구하겠습니다.
Agreed.
동의했습니다.
I've stayed a few days here.
나는 여기에 며칠 동안 머물렀다.
At that time we had an agreement.
그 당시 우리는 합의를 했습니다.
Chief Kimura of the Military Police Headquarters wants to see me.
헌병사령부 기무라 반장이 나를 만나고 싶어한다.
Until now it is still not visible.
지금까지는 여전히 보이지 않습니다.
I've told Village Chief Mu,
무 마을 이장에게 말했어요.
It is just...
그건 그저...
Just what?
그냥 뭐?
Brother Huang, I am not covering anything up.
황 형제님, 저는 아무 것도 은폐하지 않습니다.
Your gift is not heavy enough.
당신의 선물은 충분히 무겁지 않습니다.
I've given everyone a list of the names of transportation station number five
5번 역의 이름 목록을 모두에게 주었습니다.
giving is still not heavy enough.
베푸는 일은 아직 충분히 무겁지 않습니다.
Despite arresting several people
여러 사람을 체포했음에도 불구하고
but just an ordinary person.
하지만 그냥 평범한 사람이에요.
The Military Police Soldier Commander's appetite was growing.
헌병대 사령관의 식욕이 커지고있었습니다.
Yumo bookstore security code,
유모서점 보안코드,
I've given it to you.
나는 그것을 당신에게 주었다.
Not arresting people
사람을 체포하지 않음
You can't blame me right?
나를 비난할 수는 없잖아요?
The name of this Plum Blossom Si,
이 매화씨의 이름은,
sister Huang ever heard of it?
황 자매님, 들어본 적 있나요?
Plum blossom four.
매화 넷.
Our people?
우리 사람들?
Chinese Communist Party codenamed Meihua Si.
중국 공산당 코드명은 메이화시(Meihua Si)이다.
Has been hiding in Taihe Company for a long time.
오랫동안 태화회사에 숨어 지내왔습니다.
Now I
지금
I have a clear target of suspicion.
의심할 대상이 뚜렷해요.
As long as you help me find evidence,
증거를 찾는 데 도움을 주시는 한,
I promise,
약속해요
not only arranged for you to meet Village Chief Mu,
무 마을 촌장을 만나도록 주선했을 뿐만 아니라,
I will fulfill
나는 성취할 것이다
I will fulfill them one by one, will not deny them.
나는 그것들을 하나씩 이행할 것이고, 그것들을 부정하지 않을 것이다.
But I don't know him.
하지만 나는 그를 모른다.
How can I help you?
어떻게 도와 드릴까요?
Help me read the newspaper
신문 읽는 것을 도와주세요
what does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Bulletin board.
게시판.
Those of you who want to find someone else.
다른 사람을 찾고 싶은 분들.
Why?
왜?
The word "seeking brother" to pay the new year,
새해를 맞이하기 위해 "형님을 구합니다"라는 단어,
is our secret code.
우리의 비밀 코드입니다.
Continue.
계속하다.
Brother has been in Shanghai for several days,
형은 며칠 동안 상하이에 있었는데,
This means wanting to connect.
연결하고 싶다는 뜻이다.
I can't find you at your original address, 220.
원래 주소인 220에서는 찾을 수 없습니다.
This is the time.
지금이 바로 그때이다.
This afternoon at 2:20
오늘 오후 2시 20분
The second sister at Zhou Jian's house
Zhou Jian 집의 둘째 여동생
3rd younger brother, Shan Ming was very worried about him.
셋째 남동생 Shan Ming은 그를 매우 걱정했습니다.
Boat?
보트?
Mountain.
산.
Is there a place in Shanghai that says "Zhou and Shan"?
상하이에 "Zhou and Shan"이라는 곳이 있나요?
Taman Zhoushan.
타만 저우산.
The connection location is Zhoushan Park.
연결 위치는 Zhoushan Park입니다.
Correct.
옳은.
Now I am staying temporarily on the fifth floor of Pujiang Inn.
지금은 포장여관 5층에 임시로 머물고 있습니다.
Pujiang is a place associated with water.
포강(浦江)은 물과 관련된 곳이다.
Is there a pond in Zhoushan Park?
저우산 공원에 연못이 있나요?
I once went to Zhoushan Park.
나는 한때 Zhoushan 공원에 갔다.
Pond?
연못?
There isn't any.
아무것도 없습니다.
If there's water,
물이 있으면,
there is a fountain.
분수가 있습니다.
It's a fountain
분수예요
the fifth floor is the fifth bench.
5층은 다섯 번째 벤치이다.
That means 14.20 this afternoon,
오늘 오후 14시 20분을 의미합니다.
di Taman Zhoushan,
디 타만 저우산,
beside the fountain,
분수대 옆에는
must be CCP.
CCP여야 합니다.
Good luck.
행운을 빌어요.
Cheers.
건배.
Until found.
발견될 때까지.
This.
이것.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
One more time.
한번 더.
Good.
좋은.
Why stop the mission?
임무를 왜 중단하나요?
You've missed the best opportunity.
당신은 최고의 기회를 놓쳤습니다.
But I already have a clue
하지만 난 이미 단서를 갖고 있어
give me one more day.
하루만 더 시간을 주세요.
This is an order.
이것은 명령입니다.
Good.
좋은.
Then you can tell me
그럼 나한테 말해도 돼
what is in the magpie's hand?
까치 손에 있는 게 뭐야?
It doesn't matter if I tell you.
내가 말해도 상관없습니다.
A formula
공식
formula?
공식?
Correct
옳은
the Chinese Communist Party plans
중국 공산당의 계획
will gradually issue sideways coins
점차적으로 사이드웨이 코인을 발행할 예정입니다.
at banks in the border areas of Shaanxi and Ganning,
산시성(陝西省)과 간닝(甘寧) 국경지역 은행에서
to replace French money
프랑스 돈을 대체하기 위해
and build their own financial system.
그리고 그들만의 금융 시스템을 구축하세요.
Apart from that, they are also developing
그 외에도 그들은 또한 개발 중입니다.
special paper for printing money
돈을 인쇄하는 특수 용지
making their currency difficult to counterfeit.
화폐 위조가 어렵게 됩니다.
Therefore, within the squad,
따라서 선수단 내에서는
sent two special agents to scout in Yan'an,
옌안을 정찰하기 위해 두 명의 특수 요원을 보냈습니다.
to investigate border money printing
국경 돈 인쇄를 조사하기 위해
and also information about the publisher.
출판사에 대한 정보도 있습니다.
The magpie is one of them.
까치가 그중 하나입니다.
But unexpectedly this person
그런데 의외로 이 사람이
after getting mysterious information
신비한 정보를 얻은 후
he immediately used this as a threat
그는 즉시 이것을 위협으로 사용했습니다.
for us to pay sky-high prices?
우리가 하늘 높은 가격을 지불하기 위해?
How can there be such scum in the government?
어떻게 정부에 이런 쓰레기가 있을 수 있나요?
Chongqing can't wait
충칭은 기다릴 수 없어
they had to get the formula as soon as possible
그들은 가능한 한 빨리 공식을 얻어야 했어요
So, Boss Dai...
그럼 다이보스...
Already agreed to a sky-high price.
이미 높은 가격에 동의했습니다.
The person he sent has arrived in Shanghai.
그가 보낸 사람이 상하이에 도착했습니다.
They will immediately make a transaction.
그들은 즉시 거래를 할 것입니다.
I don't understand
모르겠어요
why do we want a money printing paper formula
왜 우리는 돈 인쇄 용지 공식을 원하는가?
if we fake it
우리가 그걸 속이면
can counterfeit real money
진짜 돈을 위조할 수 있다
and put it in the border area
그리고 국경지역에 넣어주세요.
new financial system
새로운 금융 시스템
financial system
재무 시스템
will collapse in an instant.
한순간에 무너집니다.
We don't have to fire a single shot
한 발도 쏠 필요 없어
to destroy the nest of the Communist Party.
공산당의 둥지를 파괴하기 위해.
But doing it like this,
그런데 이렇게 하면,
isn't it a violation at all?
전혀 위반 아닌가요?
statement of cooperation between the state and the Communist Party.
국가와 공산당 간의 협력 선언문.
You're too innocent.
당신은 너무 결백합니다.
When have the Kuomintang and the Communist Party ever had real cooperation?
국민당과 공산당이 실제로 협력한 적이 언제였습니까?
Previously restricted collusion,
이전에는 공모가 제한되었으며,
now it has become a real anti-communist.
이제는 진정한 반공주의자가 되었습니다.
In the Communist Party,
공산당에서는
there are many brave warriors
용감한 전사들이 많아요
they are willing to sacrifice their lives
그들은 기꺼이 목숨을 바칠 각오가 되어 있다
sacrifice their own lives
자신의 목숨을 희생
they are our comrades in arms.
그들은 우리의 전우입니다.
Now we let our comrades in arms become enemies.
이제 우리는 전우들을 적이 되게 놔두었습니다.
How is this different from the others?
이것이 다른 것과 어떻게 다른가요?
Your thoughts are very scary.
당신의 생각은 매우 무섭습니다.
Do you want to be a traitor?
배신자가 되고 싶나요?
Actually who is the traitor?
사실 배신자는 누구인가?
You make sure first.
먼저 확인하세요.
That's the fifth bench?
다섯번째 벤치인가요?
We're pretending to talk here
우리 여기서 얘기하는 척하고 있어
wait for Chen Jia Ping and Jie's people to appear
Chen Jia Ping과 Jie의 사람들이 나타날 때까지 기다리십시오
immediately arrested
즉시 체포
this time Chen Jia Ping definitely couldn't escape
이번에는 Chen Jia Ping이 확실히 탈출할 수 없었습니다.
look at her makeup
그 사람 화장 좀 봐
There he is?
거기 있어요?
He sat in fifth place.
그는 5위에 앉았습니다.
He must have come to cooperate.
그 사람은 협력하러 왔나 봐요.
What should we do?
우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
The cooperating person has not yet appeared
협력자는 아직 나타나지 않았습니다
Chen Jia Ping seemed to be about to leave
Chen Jia Ping이 곧 떠날 것 같았습니다.
not true
사실이 아니다
just now
방금
his hand touched under the bench.
그의 손이 벤치 아래에 닿았습니다.
Maybe not to work together.
어쩌면 함께 일하지 않을 수도 있습니다.
He must have exchanged information.
그 사람이 정보를 교환한 게 틀림없어요.
Catch it immediately!
즉시 잡아라!
Catch him, caught red-handed.
그를 잡아라, 적발됐다.
Road!
도로!
A little faster!
조금 더 빠르게!
Fast!
빠른!
Fast.
빠른.
Do not move.
이동하지 않습니다.
Raise your hand
손 들어
chen Jia Ping
첸 지아 핑
Do you still want to avoid it this time?
이번에도 피하고 싶나요?
You...
너...
Ketua Zhao.
케투아 자오.
Why are you always everywhere?
당신은 왜 항상 어디에나 있나요?
What are you here for?
당신이 여기 왜 왔나?
Why am I here?
내가 왜 여기에 있는 걸까요?
I'm still asking why you came
난 아직도 네가 왜 왔냐고 묻고 있어
why are you pointing a gun at me?
왜 나한테 총을 겨누는 거야?
have you registered a permit to hold weapons in the French concession?
프랑스 조계지에서 무기 보유 허가를 등록하셨나요?
What are you holding under the bench
벤치 밑에 무엇을 들고 있나요?
seat?
좌석?
There isn't anything.
아무것도 없습니다.
Check the body.
본체를 확인하세요.
Chief.
셰프.
This is their territory
이곳은 그들의 영토다
are you sure you want to do that?
정말 그렇게 하고 싶나요?
We have this ability,
우리에겐 이런 능력이 있고,
check the body.
몸을 확인해 보세요.
Go away.
저리 가요.
Search the bench.
벤치를 검색해 보세요.
There isn't any.
아무것도 없습니다.
Youre here.
너 여기 있네.
Police Clemish.
경찰 클레미쉬.
You guys?
여러분?
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Chief,
셰프,
there was a misunderstanding between us.
우리 사이에 오해가 있었어요.
Correct.
옳은.
That's right, right?
그렇죠?
That's it.
그게 다야.
Where is Captain Clemish?
클레미쉬 선장은 어디에 있나요?
He will return to France for a while.
그는 잠시 동안 프랑스로 돌아갈 예정이다.
He asked me to look after his dog.
그는 나에게 자신의 개를 돌봐달라고 요청했습니다.
Sheriff Clemson walks the dog here every day.
클렘슨 보안관은 매일 이곳에서 개를 산책시킵니다.
So, I'll just leave it at that.
그래서 나는 그것을 그대로 두겠습니다.
Why?
왜?
Ketua Zhao
케투아 자오
do you mind?
괜찮으세요?
No opinion.
의견이 없습니다.
Do not mind.
상관 없어.
No comment. You pointed a gun at me earlier.
코멘트가 없습니다. 아까 나한테 총을 겨눴잖아.
Why
왜
want to shoot me?
나를 쏘고 싶어?
Must be wrong
틀렸음에 틀림없어
keep all the guns.
총을 모두 보관하세요.
If it's wrong
잘못된 경우
do what must be done.
해야 할 일을 하십시오.
Sheriff Clemens.
클레멘스 보안관.
Have a safe trip.
안전한 여행 되세요.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Until found.
발견될 때까지.
Chairman of the Fifth Transportation Station, Jin Ming
제5교통역 회장 Jin Ming
betrayed after being captured
체포된 후 배신당함
many comrades were betrayed by him
많은 동지들이 그에게 배신당했다
captured or sacrificed.
체포되거나 희생되었습니다.
The loss is very painful.
상실은 매우 고통스럽습니다.
Be sure to find the Jinming location
진밍 위치를 꼭 찾아보세요
and report it immediately to the organization.
그리고 즉시 해당 기관에 보고하세요.
If there is an emergency,
긴급상황이 발생한 경우,
call this number 65542.2.
이 번호를 65542.2로 불러주세요.
Once the phone rings, hang up.
전화벨이 울리면 끊으세요.
Call again
다시 전화하세요
parrot
앵무새
based on Jin Ming level,
진밍 레벨을 기준으로,
he can unlock the secret code of the link.
그는 링크의 비밀 코드를 풀 수 있습니다.
But what he didn't know was,
하지만 그가 몰랐던 것은,
You contact the organization before being arrested
체포되기 전에 해당 조직에 연락
before being arrested.
체포되기 전에.
So the secret code for the parrot contacted me
그래서 앵무새의 비밀번호가 나한테 연락이 왔어
has been replaced with a second level secret code.
두 번째 수준의 비밀 코드로 대체되었습니다.
It cannot be solved by him.
그 사람이 해결해줄 수는 없어요.
However, maybe you can take advantage of this
그러나 어쩌면 당신은 이것을 활용할 수 있습니다
to lock Jinming.
진밍을 잠그기 위해.
Actually in the hands of Luo Guanqun or Zhao An?
실제로 Luo Guanqun 또는 Zhao An의 손에 있습니까?
First thing,
우선,
look for someone to make a new declaration.
새로운 선언을 해줄 사람을 찾으세요.
Place the contents of the paper in the notification section,
공지란에 논문의 내용을 넣고,
however, it should be published tomorrow.
그러나 그것은 내일 출판되어야 합니다.
Second thing,
두 번째로,
Why? Look at me.
왜? 날 봐.
Should be.
해야한다.
Tomorrow at 2 pm
내일 오후 2시
you disguised yourself as me,
당신은 나로 변장했어요.
go to Zhoushan Park.
저우산 공원으로 가세요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
But if anyone notices
하지만 누군가 눈치채면
that person is you,
그 사람이 바로 너야.
You have to think of a reason
이유를 생각해봐야지
Tell them why you appeared here.
당신이 여기에 나타난 이유를 그들에게 말해주세요.
Waiter.
웨이터.
Two!
둘!
Where is guest room 612?
612호실은 어디에 있나요?
The master came out earlier.
주인이 더 일찍 나왔어요.
Is this brat going to lie to us?
이 새끼가 우리한테 거짓말을 할 셈인가?
What code?
어떤 코드?
Absolutely not true.
절대 사실이 아닙니다.
He was not that brave.
그는 그렇게 용감하지 않았습니다.
There must be an error.
오류가 있어야 합니다.
After he comes home ask clearly,
그가 집에 오면 명확하게 물어보세요.
also quite brave
그것도 꽤 용감하게
still dare to go out.
아직도 감히 나가려고 합니다.
You're a new resident, right?
당신은 새로운 주민이군요, 그렇죠?
Never seen it before.
전에는 본 적이 없습니다.
New arrivals arrive on their first day of work.
새로 도착한 사람들은 근무 첫날에 도착합니다.
You're the one who just arrived
방금 도착한 사람이 바로 너야
Please help, Brother.
도와주세요, 형제님.
What did you come to get?
무엇을 얻으러 오셨나요?
Guest number 61 wants scented soap,
61번 손님은 향이 나는 비누를 원하고,
it's there, right?
거기 있지, 그렇지?
It's?
그것은?
This soap seems moist.
이 비누는 촉촉한 것 같아요.
Brother, I've brought it.
형님, 제가 가져왔습니다.
I know you can't smoke here.
여기서는 담배를 피울 수 없다는 걸 알아요.
Don't talk carelessly outside.
밖에서 함부로 이야기하지 마세요.
Chief.
셰프.
Earlier someone came into room 612.
조금 전에 누군가가 612호실에 들어왔습니다.
Who's that?
저 사람은 누구야?
Waiter
웨이터
waiter.
웨이터.
No need to make a fuss anymore
더 이상 소란을 피울 필요가 없어요
Is there anyone?
거기 아무도 없나요?
Hello, sir.
안녕하세요 선생님.
Pujiang Hotel.
푸장 호텔.
House six one two.
집 여섯 하나 둘.
Hey!
여기요!
Sister.
자매.
I saw the Chief earlier
아까 국장님을 봤어요
seems to be heading towards the grass.
잔디밭으로 향하고 있는 것 같습니다.
You pay attention.
당신은주의를 기울입니다.
Good.
좋은.
Chief.
셰프.
Do not move.
이동하지 않습니다.
Put the gun down.
총을 내려놓으세요.
It's me
나야
why are you like this?
왜 이러세요?
Where are you going?
어디 가세요?
The food at this hotel is very bad.
이 호텔의 음식은 매우 나쁩니다.
I went out to eat some delicious food.
맛있는 음식을 먹으러 나갔습니다.
Aren't you afraid of your people looking for you?
사람들이 당신을 찾는 것이 두렵지 않습니까?
You don't even recognize me.
당신은 나를 알아보지도 못합니다.
What am I afraid of?
나는 무엇을 두려워합니까?
We didn't arrest anyone today.
오늘 우리는 누구도 체포하지 않았습니다.
Not caught.
잡히지 않았습니다.
Impossible.
불가능한.
The code I translated was not wrong.
제가 번역한 코드는 틀리지 않았습니다.
We'll talk inside.
우리는 내부에 얘기하자.
Sister.
자매.
Didn't get caught, right?
잡히지 않았죠?
Thank you earlier.
미리 감사드립니다.
Don't hesitate, don't hesitate.
망설이지 마세요, 망설이지 마세요.
I have a pack of cigarettes
나는 담배 한 갑을 가지고 있다
given by a friend
친구가 준
he said it was pretty good
그 사람은 꽤 괜찮다고 했어
but I don't smoke.
하지만 나는 담배를 피우지 않습니다.
How about giving it to you, Big Brother?
빅 브라더, 너한테 주는 건 어때?
I can't afford to buy
구매할 여유가 없어요
I can't afford it.
나는 그것을 감당할 수 없습니다.
That's right, right?
그렇죠?
If not, just like this
그렇지 않다면 이대로
chief administrator
최고 관리자
always walk around here.
항상 이 근처를 돌아다니세요.
Brother, if you want to smoke, go outside
형, 담배피고 싶으면 밖에 나가세요
for smokers.
흡연자를 위한.
I'll help you watch it here.
여기에서 시청할 수 있도록 도와드리겠습니다.
Brother, come up.
형님, 올라오세요.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Otherwise our people
그렇지 않으면 우리 사람들은
If I knew, I would cooperate with you.
알았다면 협조해 주었을 텐데.
First, we issue a contact code.
먼저 연락처 코드를 발급합니다.
Then suddenly cancel the connection.
그런 다음 갑자기 연결을 취소하십시오.
There's no point in saying all this.
이 모든 것을 말해도 소용이 없습니다.
Brother Huang,
황 형제,
for your sake,
당신을 위해서,
Village Chief Mu and I ran here and there.
무 마을 이장과 나는 이리저리 뛰어다녔다.
The boss also agreed
사장님도 동의하셨어요
to send you
당신을 보내기 위해
to the new government construction department.
새 정부 건설부에.
So, you...
그래서 당신은...
Still have some reservations,
아직 예약이 남아있는데,
wasting our good intentions.
우리의 좋은 의도를 낭비하고 있습니다.
Tonight I want to meet Village Chief Mu.
오늘 밤에는 무 마을 이장을 만나고 싶습니다.
Please tell me.
알려주세요.
You will definitely be given a big prize.
반드시 큰 상을 받게 될 것입니다.
Same with me.
나도 마찬가지다.
I want to meet Kimura.
기무라를 만나고 싶어요.
Good.
좋은.
I will report to Village Chief Mu now.
지금 무 마을 이장에게 보고하겠습니다.
Didn't have time to report to superiors
상사에게 보고할 시간이 없었다
must be killed immediately
즉시 죽여야 한다
brother
형제
The smoke...
연기...
Sister.
자매.
Just now the foreman came
지금 막 감독님 오셨어요
the chief administrator said not to make a fuss
최고관리자가 소란 피우지 말라고 했어
lower your voice.
목소리를 낮추세요.
Your scent is really nice.
네 향기가 정말 좋구나.
Thank You.
감사합니다.
Next time if there is a problem,
다음에 문제가 생기면
Good.
좋은.
Please look for me.
저를 찾아주세요.
Sister.
자매.
Then I'll deliver the goods.
그럼 물건을 배달해 드리겠습니다.
Go, go.
가, 가.
Delivering goods.
상품을 배송합니다.
Good, go.
좋아요, 가세요.
Hello, sir.
안녕하세요 선생님.
Change bed linen.
침대 린넨을 갈아주세요.
I'm in the bathroom.
나는 화장실에 있어요.
Come in.
올.